(Sheldon:)Those must be neurons.
(Sheldon:)Oh, they're so thick
and beautiful.
(Amy:)Those are your
eyelashes, move.
(Amy:)Well, Sheldon...
(Amy:)I see astrocytes.
(Amy:)Our combined skin cells are now
(Amy:)a primitive neural network.
(Sheldon:)I have such a profound
(Sheldon:)sense of creation.
I ju... it's like
when I hatched Sea-Monkeys,
(Sheldon:)except that this
is from my DNA,
(Sheldon:)so this is like...
Me-Monkeys.
(Amy:)These cells come
from both of us.
Yeah, but Us-Monkeys
doesn't pop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wait!
We-Monkeys, there you go.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)When can we start
running tests on it?
(Amy:)No reason we can't
start right now.
(Sheldon:)What stimulus should we
introduce it to first?
L-Light, sound, temperature...
Oh! Oh! Let's
expose it to images
of me and you and see
who it likes better.
(Amy:)Sheldon, this is a rudimentary
collection of neurons.
(Amy:)I mean, it's remarkable,